THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy.
洛根·罗伊 介意我拍个照吗
Logan Roy! Mind if I get a quick photo?
-我超崇拜你  -退后
- I'm a big fan. - Step back.
超级超级崇拜 我喜欢你的工作
Big, big fan. I-I love your work.
喜欢你做的所有事 你的种族歧视和厌女癖...
I love everything you do. I love all the racism, misogyny...
离远点
Step off.
-真是太酷了  -保安
- It's really cool stuff! - Security!
洛根 看这边
Logan, over here!
尝尝老子的尿吧
My fuckin' piss!
你他妈个搞垄断的人渣
You're fuckin' monopolist scum!
-进您眼睛里了吗  -去死吧
- Did it get in your eye? - I hope you die!
能麻烦你开下门吗
Can you open this up, please?
-不准别人进来  -好的 后退
- I want no one else in here. - All right, stay back.
能拿件衬衫到这边吗
Can we get another shirt down here?
罗伊先生在外面出了点事
We had an incident outside with Mr. Roy.
你说得有多少人在那袋子里撒尿
How many people do you think pissed in that bag
才能凑齐那么一大包啊
to get all that piss?
全都是尿
I mean, it's just urine.
我没事 我没事
I'm good, I'm good.
不用这么大惊小怪 我没事
No fuss, no fuss, I'm good. OK?
-你还好吗  -很好
- Are you OK? - Fine.
别都围过来
Don't get all over me.
-行吗  -好的
- Ok? - Ok.
这些信托基金的视频简直了
These trust fund YouTube shits.
天呐 我们有过几个这种人...
God, we had a couple of these guys...
我还在呢 好吗
I'm here. OK?
现在我明白了
Now, I understand
你想让我把所有想法都告诉你
you want me to go through my every thought with you.
我很感激终于有机会跟您讨论
I appreciate finally getting a chance
您正在考虑的这些重要举措 没错
to talk through these very major moves you're considering, yes.
我们已经了解到
We've become aware
一些可以够得到的理想资产
of some very desirable assets that are available.
一批本地电视台
A block of local TV stations.
它们的价值被低估了
Highly undervalued.
电视视...
Teevvvee...
我还记得那些东西
I remember those.
我的健身房里现在还有一台
We still have one of those in my gym.
有我儿子大学时一起酗酒的朋友
It's so great to have the wisdom of my son's
贡献他的智慧真是太好了
college drinking buddy in the room.
我超爱他问我要钱的方式
I just love the way he asks me for money.
当然 我懂
No, I get it.
但存在一个紧迫的问题 对吗
But there is a pressing issue, right?
这是大战略里的一步棋
Well, it's part of a larger strategy.
当然... 这些我都明白
No, I... I get all that.
我只是... 好吧
I'm just... All right.
我觉得现在的问题是 先生
I think the issue here, sir,
每个人都他妈恨死你了
is that everyone fucking hates you.
有失就有得
It's cloudy, it's sunny.
您想要推进一次大规模的
You want to push through a massive
触动政治神经的买断
politically sensitive buy-up,
这是我早上喝咖啡时读到的
and I'm reading this over my morning cappuccino.
报纸上说 您的家族是个恐怖秀
It says your family is a horror show
正在毁灭美国
and it's destroying America.
也许我们应该买下这家
Maybe we should buy this.
肯德尔对您提起了诉讼
Kendall launched a lawsuit against you.
您又炒掉董事会的一半人马
You have fired half of your board.
您的首席运营官就他妈是个玩笑
Your COO is a fucking joke.
哥们 外面就是这么传的 谁在乎真假呢
Bro, that's what people are saying. Who cares if it's true?
人们说 他是个吸毒的太子爷
People say that he's a coked-up dauphin
不谙世事 幼稚无知
that doesn't know shit from Shinola,
还说你俩形同陌路
and that the two of you aren't even talking to each other,
这个我也感受得到
which I am getting a vibe of.
这些我都懒得管
Now, I could care less,
但就连这次先声夺人的本地电视台收购
but even the advance whispers of this local TV deal
都激起民愤
have people so mad at you
他们都在街上向您泼尿了
that they're throwing piss at you on the street.
我们还不知道到底是不是尿
We don't know that it was actually piss.
那就是尿
It was piss.
您想来个大血拼
You want to go on a shopping spree.
我相信您 但能不能先修补好形象呢
I trust you, but can we please fix the visuals?
这是家族企业
This is a family business.
可家都要散了
But the family is fucked,
会影响到股票
and it's hurting the stock.
翻译: 奶啾
翻译: 我的后面是猪精
翻译: Graaace
翻译: 这个家伙
翻译: Ciaran
翻译: 李木木
翻译: 海顿
翻译: 橙砸
时间轴: Heiforn
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 雨人
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继     承
第 一 季  第７集
"奥斯特里茨"
监制: 渡渡
每当战争考验这个国家时
Whenever war has tested this nation,
我们都能大获全胜
we have won out.
我认为这就是我们面临的现状
And that is what I believe we face right now.
无非是一场
Nothing less than a war
与人类不平等之间的战争
against human inequality,
一场在所难免的战争
a war we must fight
阻止可观的权力和财富
to stop unimaginably vast power and riches
落入
falling into the hands
极少数人的手中
of an impossibly small number of men.
我不畏此战
I'm not afraid of this fight.
我知道你们也不怕
I know you're not either.
战斗在此打响
This fight starts here.
我是吉尔·伊维斯 我批准此条消息
I'm Gil Eavis, and I approved this message.
我不明白 这种阶级战争的鬼话
I don't know, this class war shit,
你不觉得有点幼稚吗
don't you find it a little jejune?
-幼稚  -对 就是不成熟的意思
- Jejune? - Yeah. It means juvenile.
是 我... 我知道什么意思
Yeah, I... I know what it means.
我就是觉得 只有混蛋会这么说
I just thought only assholes said it.
-不 我不觉得幼稚  -你是要惹毛我吗
- No, I do not find it jejune. - Is this you pulling my hair?
不然为什么叫我来看这个呢 你找错人了
Because why did you bring me in for this? I'm not a good fit.
我坚信他会是
I genuinely believe he's gonna
美国的下一任总统
be the next president of the United States.
你了解我的 我什么都不信
And you know me, I don't believe in anything.
你现在和乔伊丝完事了吗
Are you finished with Joyce now?
是的 她走不远了
Yeah. That's as far as she'll go.
好 像你这样的人能为吉尔所用
OK. Gil could really use someone like you.
这不会有问题吗
And this wouldn't be a problem?
什么
What?
气氛
The atmosphere.
我觉得只要我们说清楚就行
I think as long as we have clarity.
-没错 说清楚  -对
- Yeah. Right. Clarity. - Right.
那就明确一下
And to be clear,
在任何地点 任何时间
at absolutely any place at any time,
不计后果
with absolutely no consequences,
我都想操你
I would fuck you,
而且极其想操你
and will want desperately to fuck you.
这是一种永恒不变的状态
And that is just a permanent state of affairs.
我只想表明我的立场
I just want you to know that is my position.
一切都由你掌控
You have all the power.
你可以随心所欲
You can do whatever you want with it.
我们怎么也做起这档子事了 格丽
When did we start having to do this shit, Gerri?
采访你的记者是里奥·洛伦泽蒂
The journalist is Leo Lorenzetti.
标语是 "动荡后的再聚首"
The piece will be, "After the turmoil, the coming together."
在您儿子的农场
At your son's ranch.
一个家庭 一代王朝
A family, a dynasty,
一个美国式传奇
an American story.
这将是非常引人注目的系列
It'll be a very compelling package.
这家伙又是干嘛的 艾隆是谁
And what's this shit? Who's this guy Alon?
他是很有声誉的企业治疗师
Very highly regarded corporate therapist.
哈佛商学院毕业
Harvard Business School.
一家世界五百强公司的前首席财务官
Former CFO at a Fortune 500.
他之前为文莱的苏丹[文莱的国家元首]
He just worked with the Sultan of Brunei,
和博尔基亚亲王一家工作[文莱皇室成员]
and the Bolkiah family.
他们必须全部到场吗
Do they all have to be there?
叛徒也要来吗
Does the traitor come too?
很显然 由您来决定
Well, obviously, that's your choice.
但这想要传达出的信息
But the message, I think,
我认为是一家人在沙漠中的重聚
is a family reunited in the desert.
反省过错 重拾亲情
A time to reflect, regroup.
您要达成的目标是家庭团结
Family unity is kind of what you're going for.
-行 行 行  -直白地说 洛根
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.  - And frankly, Logan,
如果你能让肯德尔撤诉
if you can get Kendall to drop the lawsuit,
我们这边的收购就好办了
everything becomes cleaner for us, acquisition-wise.
好吧 但我不会低声下气的
OK. Well, I'm not groveling.
给罗慕路斯打电话
Get Romulus on the phone.
先把邮件搞定
Let's do the email.
你好 小西
Hey, Shiv.
是老康 听着 你收到老爸的邮件了吗
It's Con. Listen, did you get this email from Dad
关于心理治疗的
about therapy?
因为这
'Cause, I mean,
这实在是 不可思议
this is, like, wow!
所以我需要确认一下这不是
So I just need to check that it's not
那种垃圾邮件之类的
one of those spam things or something.
就这样 回聊
All right, so call me.
我喜欢吉尔... 大家都喜欢他 他很棒...
I like Gil... people like Gil, he's great...
但我总感觉如果他赢得选举
but I have a sneaking feeling that if he won an election
有可能会把我和我认识的人排成一排射成筛子
he'd probably like to line me up and everyone I know and shoot us.
-我操 不可能  -怎么了
- Holy fuck. No way.  - What?
等一下
Hang on.
-怎么了  -你看到邮件了么
- Hey.  - Have you seen this?
这怎么可能 老爸要安排治疗
I can't believe it. Dad's doing therapy?
我还以为你不会跟我说话了
I thought you weren't talking to me because
因为我没告诉你投票的事
I didn't tell you about the vote.
我是没有 但这什么鬼
I'm not. But what the fuck.
这不扯淡吗
Very much the fuck.
究极扯淡的那种
Very much the fuck indeed.
家里的硬汉要妥协了 大家都被邀请了
The big man is breakin' down, and everyone's invited.
除了肯德尔
Well, not Kendall.
-所有人  -太扯淡了
- Everybody.  - This is bullshit.
他想干什么
What's he doing?
-我得挂了 回聊  -抱歉 罗伊先生...
- Gotta go. See ya. - Please, Mr. Roy...
-我需要和肯德尔聊聊  -他现在没空
- I need to talk to Kendall.  - He's not available.
没空是什么意思
What do you mean he's not available?
他在忙什么 拼他妈的乐高吗
What is he doing, playing with his fucking Legos?
他现在肯定闲得慌
He's nothing but available.
他现在不在
He isn't here right now.
好吧 我知道你在忽悠我
Well, I know that's not true,
就让我进去 行吗
so just come on, OK?
他好几个星期都没回来了
He hasn't been here for weeks.
-很抱歉  -放屁 听着
- I'm sorry.  - Bullshit. OK, look,
你能给他留个口信吗
will you just give him a message?
-不能 谢谢你  -告诉他...
- No, thank you.  - Tell him...
"不能 谢谢你" ...
"No, thank you" ...
让他回一下邮件
Tell him to reply to the email,
他必须到场 知道吗
that he has to come. OK?
告诉他...
Tell him that...
那啥 老爸想...
Hey. Dad wants...
没戏
Hey. Um, no.
不 我觉得他不会去
No, I don't think he's gonna play ball.
他不愿跟我说话 撤诉就更别想了
He's not talking. No way he's gonna drop the lawsuit.
知道了 没关系的 罗曼
OK, that's fine, Roman.
-没成吗  -没
- No?  - No.
行吧 备用方案
OK. Plan B.
"黑羊[败家子]行动"
Operation Black Sheep.
-喂  -喂 你还好吗
- Hey.  - Hey. You OK?
还行 我挺好 怎么了
Yeah, I'm fine. What's up?
对了 我们什么时候交接
Oh, what time are we doing the pickup?
你看过索菲社交账号的内容吗
Do you ever look at Sophie's Instagram?
我看的时候
I was monitoring,
有个年纪大点的孩子
and one of the older kids
把诋毁你的文章链接发了出来
linked to that shitty article about you.
什么文章
What article?
我没刻意地关注任何东西 拉瓦
I haven't been looking at anything. Deliberately, Rava.
"肯德尔·罗伊在纽约街头狂奔
"Kendall Roy ran the streets of New York,
浑身汗臭 语无伦次
sweaty and incoherent,
叫嚣着要谋权篡位
ranting about a coup against his father,
到了董事会会议室 却连个屁都不敢放
but couldn't find his way to the board room to start said coup.
他复吸了吗
Is he back on drugs?
我们无法确定
We couldn't possibly say,
但这条消息并非空穴来风"
but some people are saying that."
拉瓦 听我讲
Rava, listen to me.
这些... 这些不是真的
OK, that's... That's not true.
-是吗  -这不是真的
- Yeah. - OK? That's not true.
你以前想掩盖事实的时候
It's just that's what you used to say
也这么说来着
when it was true.
天呐 我没有吸毒 拉瓦
Jesus, I'm not using, Rava.
我... 我什么都没碰
I... I don't touch anything.
你知道的 老天爷 别这样
And you know that. Jesus Christ. Come on.
但先放下这件事
But look, unrelated,
这周末艾弗森要考试
this weekend Iverson's got his tests
如果我们扰乱他的计划 会有不好的影响
and if we break his routine, it's gonna affect things.
-你知道吗  -不会的 不
- You know?  - No. No.
操 别这样
Fuck, come on.
求你别生气
Please don't get angry.
我没... 我他妈没生气
I'm not... I'm not fucking angry.
行吗 我想见孩子们
OK? I want to see my kids.
我没吸毒 我什么都没碰
I'm not on drugs, I'm not touching drugs,
我已经戒了 我没吸毒
I don't use drugs anymore, I'm not on drugs,
我他妈的没吸毒
I'm not on fucking drugs.
你这么不停重申还挺能说服人的
Yeah, it's the paranoid rant that's so convincing.
其实我觉得你去那里很有勇气
Well, I actually think it's really brave to go.
谢谢夸奖 我可是个英雄
Oh, thank you. I'm a hero.
你能想象吗
Can you imagine?
跟康纳 爸爸和罗曼谈心
Connor, Dad, Roman, feelings?
感觉就像把一大袋冲锋枪扔进软体玩具区
It's gonna be like tossing a bag of Uzis into the soft play area.
我知道你爸不会相信
I know your dad doesn't believe
你不知道肯德尔想干什么
you didn't know what Kendall was up to,
他还对你恶言相向
and he spoke abominably to you.
还有 就目前来看
And, um, just for context,
你觉得这周末合适
do you think it would be appropriate this weekend,
我搭桥牵线
in a bridge-building way,
跟洛根说上话吗
for me to be speaking to Logan, or no?
做你认为对的事就好了
Just do what you think is right.
也对 我知道了 那我就
Yeah, sure. I got it. I just, you know,
我想得到你的支持
I want to have your back,
当然 你也有我的支持
and, uh, there's also my back,
我们就是所向披靡的野兽
and, you know, we're a beast with two backs.
我知道了 你自己决定就好
I get it. You're your own guy.
我不会评头论足的
I won't judge you.
当然 我知道 我知道
Yeah, sure, I know that. I know that.
-你好  -你好 玛西娅
- Hi!  - Hey, Marcia!
-你好  -你好 老爸
- Hi!  - Hey, Dad!
欢迎来到奥斯特里茨
Welcome to Austerlitz!
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
-真壮观  -是啊
- Ah. It exists!  - Yeah.
奥斯特里茨 你买这的时候就叫这个名字吗
Austerlitz? Was this the name when you bought it?
旧名号有点种族歧视意味
Oh, it was racially insensitive,
所以他取了个新名字
so he picked a new one.
要不要我带你参观下里面
Do you want me to show you inside?
你好 康纳
Hi, Connor.
你好 卡洛丽娜
Hi, Karolina.
儿子 你有没有安排好地方让他们准备起来
So, son, have you got somewhere for them to set up?
你还要忙工作吗
So you're also working?
就只有几个来照相的伙计
Just a few folks doing photographs and stuff.
-是吗...  -记录一切
- Oh? Uh... - Chroniclers of everything.
好吧
Ok.
好的 没问题
OK. You bet.
-很棒的地方 空间很大  -没错
- Great place. Plenty of space. - Yeah.
这个可以有
This works.
那就好
Oh, good.
我看见你了
Hey! I see you!
-来了  -来了
- Hey! - Hey!
你好
Hi!
向都市精英致以问候
Hello to the metropolitan elite!
欢迎来到真正的美国
Welcome to the real America.
人民公仆
Oh, man of the people.
热爱农场的人
The people who work on his ranch.
-你好  -来抱一个
- Hi! - Let me hug you.
你觉得如何
What do you think?
不错
Wow. Yeah.
-都是棕色的  -没错 是的
- It's brown. - Yeah, it is.
-那是个教堂吗  -没错 是个小教堂
- Is that a church? - Yeah, that's the chapel.
明天我们会去那儿
We're gonna be in there tomorrow.
这个小教堂建于1878年
That chapel dates to 1878.
-酷  -是个小教堂
- Cool! - It's a chapel.
你觉得爸能迈进教堂的门吗
Do you think Dad will be able to cross the threshold?
会不会一进门就自燃了
Or will be spontaneously combust?
问得好
Good question.
要不你们先安顿好
Why don't you guys get settled in,
傍晚来参加我们的鸡尾酒会
and then join us for cocktails this evening.
兰德尔是旁边农场的主人
Randall owns the next ranch over.
我让他过来看看 打个招呼
I told him to pop in. Just wanted to say hi.
他的农药生意做得很大
He's very big in pesticides.
我并不需要农药
Uh-huh. I don't need any.
是的 人人都这么说
Yeah, that's what everybody says.
不 我总是笑他
Nah, I'm always ribbing him.
你知道吗 每几百串葡萄里就有三串
Did you know that three out of every hundred bunches of grapes
沾上的农药量超过法定标准
has over the legal limit of pesticides?
所以吃之前要洗洗
So you wash 'em.
你又不能洗肠子 毒药先生
You can't wash your colon, Mr. Poison.
为什么 我应该...
Why, I oughta...
机灵鬼 快举手投降
Smart guy, put 'em up!
洛根认为她事先知道这次政变
He thinks she knew about the coup.
所以除非小西道歉 不然他不会和她讲话的
So Logan will talk to Shiv as long as she says "Sorry."
但我觉得 从小西的立场来看
Well, I think that Shiv's position would be
她没什么可道歉的
that she's got nothing to be sorry for.
显然她很受伤
I mean, obviously she's sad,
你懂的 她很悲伤
you know, there's sadness.
我们可以强调这个
We could offer that.
内特
新短信
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
你在干什么呢
看手机
行
消息灵通点
我需要你
加入队伍 我觉得咱能联手 做好准备
好了 又有乐子了
OK. The entertainment has arrived.
这就像... 就像狂欢的前奏
This is like a... like the first stages of an orgy.
有些兴奋 可场面又超级尴尬
Kind of exciting, but also super-awkward.
-好啦 我做到了  -做到什么了
- There. I did it. - Did what?
我搞定你爸那边了
I just iced your dad.
-好哇 汤姆  -好
- Hey, Tom. - Hey.
我能...
Can I...
可以 你又不听命于我
Uh, yeah, I'm not in charge of you.
给我拿杯喝的去
But go get me a drink.
开玩笑
I'm joking.
治脑子的医生在哪儿呢
So where's the actual head doctor guy?
我怎么知道 谁都把我蒙在鼓里
I wouldn't know. No one tells me anything.
好吧 希望他能去了你一身的婊气
Well, hope he can cure your serious case of being a bitch.
操
Ow. Fuck.
滚你丫的
Fuck you.
我赌爸肯定想借这次治疗占据上风
Bet Dad's gonna try and win at therapy.
那是他还没遇到我 我可是专家
Well, he hasn't done therapy with me yet. I'm an expert.
-是吗  -没错
- Oh, yeah? - Oh, yeah.
无麻烦一身轻就是我这样
This is what it looks like when you resolve all your issues.
-信你才怪  -随便你吧
- Uh-huh. - Mm-hmm.
我的治疗师说 爸要是早点接受治疗
My guy says that if Dad had had therapy,
我就不用治了
I wouldn't need so much.
我的治疗师觉得我能挺过来简直是奇迹
My guy's surprised I got through at all.
我可不确定你都熬过来了
I'm not sure you did make it through at all.
我没觉得...
I don't think.... dee-dee, dah-doo, bah-dee...
等着瞧 我会让你相信我一切正常的
See, I will have you know I am very well-adjusted.
你... 你只是很擅长掩饰
You... you're just good at hiding it.
-帕菲特先生到了  -谢谢你
- Mr. Parfit is here. - Thank you.
好了 兰德尔
OK, Randall,
我不想赶你走
I hate to kick you out,
但我收到消息说 巨星到场了
but I have word Elvis is in the building.
-好吧  -回头见 伙计
- OK. - I'll see ya, buddy.
我想让你知道
I just want you to know
我准备向治疗师揭发你
I think I'm going to reveal to him
说我小时候你性侵我
that you sexually abused me as a child.
-你说什么  -你没听错 你就是不肯住手
- Excuse me? - Yeah. You just would not stop.
你个神经病
You are one sick puppy.
是你一直试图强奸我
You're the one who kept trying to fuck me.
你为什么要这么说 别再说了
Why would you say that? Stop saying that.
你不会真这么想吧 不会吧
You don't really think that, do you?
没 我逗[干]你呢
No. I'm fuckin' with you.
就像我小时候你干我一样
The way you fucked me as a baby.
你到底什么毛病 别这么气人
What is wrong with you? You're exasperating.
这人威胁我说要告诉大家
This one is threatening to tell the family
他小时候被我性侵过
that I diddled him when he was a little kid.
是吗 你做了吗
Oh. Right. Did you?
不 当然没有了 汤姆
No, of course not, Tom.
-康纳  -你好
- Connor. - Oh. Hi.
我是艾隆·帕菲特
Alon Parfit.
-你好  -幸会
- Hey. Hi. - Nice to see you.
-幸会  -你一定是布罗曼
- Happy you're here. - You must be Broman.
对 我是"布罗曼"
Yes, I am. Broman.
-这位是小西吧  -是的
- And Shiv. - Yeah.
-很高兴见到你  -很高兴见到你...
- Hey. Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you...?
这是汤姆 小西的未婚夫
This is Tom. Shiv's fiancé.
无关人士 跟治疗无关
Not important. To the therapy.
-说啥呢老康  -带你见见我爸
- Uh, Con? - Come meet Dad.
好的 麻烦你
Yeah, please.
-你好  -洛根·罗伊
- Hi. - Logan Roy.
-这位是玛西娅  -幸会
- This is Marcia. - Nice to meet you.
这是我的女友威拉
And this is my girlfriend Willa.
-幸会  -你好 威拉 你好吗
- Nice to meet you. - Hi, Willa, how are you?
好了 家人们...
Right. Family. Um...
我们齐聚在这栋温馨典雅的房子里
we're all gathered here in this beautiful home
因为我们有问题亟待解决
because there are things to address,
而我也坚信我们应该... 解决它们
and I believe we should... address them.
我已经解释过了
I think I explained all around
我们还会有一个
that we'll also have
庆祝我们一家团聚的小活动
a small celebration of our coming together,
顺便照照相 就在明天
with photographs, tomorrow.
没什么花里胡哨的 简约 很简约
Nothing fancy. Simple. Simple.
总之 废话不多说 让我为你们介绍
Anyway, without more ado, let me introduce to you,
艾隆·帕菲特
Alon Parfit.
大家好
Hi, everyone.
我很期待明天和大家谈心
I look forward to us all sitting down tomorrow,
但我想说 接受治疗需要巨大的勇气
but I just want to say it takes a lot of courage,
我不会辜负你们的
and that is not lost on me.
我很感动
I'm very touched.
-是的 我也是  -谢谢
- Yeah, me too. - Thanks.
这个家族四分五裂 是有后果的
This family's broken, and that has consequences.
今天漏接了一个电话
A missed phone call today,
不少在中国的员工就丢了工作
a couple dozen kids lose their jobs in China.
蝴蝶翅膀 不过要更大点
Butterfly wings, but bigger.
巨型翅膀 像翼手龙的翅膀那么大
Huge wings. Like a pterodactyl.
或是像史密森学会那样
Or the Smithsonian.
史密森学会: 唯一由美国政府资助 半官方性质的第三部门博物馆机构
那么... 携手修好我们的翅膀吧
So... let's fix our wings.
听不懂你在说啥
Barely comprehensible.
早
Morning.
加满油了 随时可以出发
It is gassed up and ready to go.
-你的钥匙  -谢谢
- Your key. - Thank you.
来这儿办大事的吗
Big plans while you're here?
也许吧
Maybe.
杀兄弑父什么的
Patricide? Fratricide?
好吧 听起来挺有意思的
OK. Sounds like fun.
-好好享受  -我会的
- Enjoy. - Oh, yeah.
-喂  -早上好
- Yeah? - Good morning.
我们到了 你准备好了吗
We're here. You ready to do this?
什么
What?
-慢着 现在吗  -没错
- No, wait. Now? - No shit.
我在圣菲[新墨西哥州首府]的酒店
I'm in a hotel in Santa Fe.
现在不行
Well, I c-can't now.
我来这里
I mean, the whole reason
是为了处理些家族事务
I came down here is to do this family thing,
就在今天 所以...
and that's today. So...
所以呢
So?
他能重新安排一下吗
Can he reschedule?
他可是大忙人一个啊
He's pretty fuckin' busy.
操
Fuck.
拒绝他可不大妙啊
Doesn't look good, turning him down.
我当然想去...
Well, obviously I want to...
来吧 小西 这事很重要
Come on, Shiv, this is huge.
-但我现在真的走不开  -亲爱的
- But I can't. Right now. - Hey, honey,
水龙头水压有点大 记得开小点
the pressure on the faucet's moderately intense, so go easy.
-我先挂了  -小西...
- I gotta go. - Shiv...
操
Fuck.
会没事的
Hey, it's gonna be OK.
It's going to be OK.
要我和你一起进去吗
Want me to come in there with you?
深入情绪泥潭 怎么样
Into the emotional swamp? Huh?
毕竟我马上要加入你们这个庞大的家族了
Pretty soon I'm gonna be part of this whole genetic carnival.
-没关系的  -你确定
- It's OK. - You sure?
当然
Yeah.
早上好
Morning.
好了 我们开始吧
OK. Let's do this.
心理治疗 往这儿走
The therapy? This way for the therapy.
就像送孩子们去上学时跟他们挥手道别
Like waving your kids off to school.
他们最好别合起伙来对付他
They better not gang up on him.
他仍然很虚弱
He's still frail.
跟上 跟上
Roll up, roll up,
吐槽大会就在前面
for the festival of grievances.
-你还好吗 儿子 -行  -那就好
- OK, son? - Yeah. -Good.
好的 很好
OK. Great.
欢迎大家 欢迎
So, welcome, welcome.
我想用几句祷文作为疗程的开始
I like to begin these things with a little prayer.
你的父母 就是他们让你如此糟糕
They fuck you up, your mom and dad.
注: 出自英国诗人菲利浦·拉金的"这就是诗"
这也许不是其本意 可事实如此
They do not mean to, but they do.
他们不仅把自己全部的缺点遗传给你
They fill you up with faults they had
还苦心孤诣地为你增加了不少
and add some extra just for you.
我一直觉得这是为接下来所做的
Now, I always think that's an interesting way
有趣的铺垫
to start these things,
但我想知道的是
but what I'd like to know is,
你们想怎么开始治疗
how you feel you would like to start this.
那...
So...
谁来说说 为什么我们今天在这儿
who's going to tell us why we are here today?
拜托 就没人想尝试一下吗
Come on. Does no one want to take a pop at the champ?
-我能说吗...  -当然
- Can I just say... - Sure.
我从未猥亵过罗曼
I never touched Roman inappropriately.
如果他说我摸过 我并没有
If he says I did, I didn't.
很高兴你澄清了这件事
Glad to clear that up.
他想开讨厌的玩笑 我只是预先制止一下
He was gonna make a horrible joke, so I'm preempting.
好了 好了
Ok. Ok.
但我觉得开始的最佳方式...
But I think the best way to start this...
如果可以的话 我先开始吧
I'll start if you'd like.
好的 请说
Yeah, Please.
我这一生所做的一切
Everything I've done in my life,
都是为了我的孩子们
I've done for my children.
我知道我犯过错
I know I've made mistakes,
但是
but,
但是为了他们 我始终拼尽全力做到最好...
but I've always tried to do the best by them...
因为... 他们是我的一切
because... they mean everything to me.
好的 很不错
OK. That was great.
谢谢
Thank you.
-很好  -是很好
- Well, that's nice. - It is nice.
当然 我也同意
Yeah, sure. Agreed.
你们对刚才听到的话有什么感想
So, what do we feel about what we just heard here?
我听到了
I mean, I hear it.
I hear it.
你的话真有意义
Big words.
说得真好
Good words.
我还在... 消化
I'm still... processing,
不过 挺好的
but yeah.
洛根 你知道在这个房间里 你施加了多少影响力吗
Logan, do you realize how much power you wield in this room?
什么意思
What do you mean?
他走到哪里都有很大影响力
He has a lot of power everywhere.
好吧 我想问的是
Okay, what I guess I'm asking is,
你对自己刚刚说的话 是什么感觉
how do you feel about what you just said?
听着 我这一生所做的一切
Look, everything I've done in my life
都是为了我的孩子们
I've done for my children.
-我知道我犯过错...  -老爸
- I know I've made mistakes... - Dad,
你不能一句话反复用
you can't just use the one sentence.
但这就是我的感受 西沃恩
But that's how I feel, Siobhan.
要是你想 我能再编点出来
I can make this shit up if you like.
听上去你已经在胡编乱造了
Sounds like you already are.
-小西  -听着 我...
- Shiv? - Look, I'm...
我的意思是
I guess where I'm coming from is
我难以投入 因为
I'm having a hard time diving in because
说实话 我在想他一开始为什么要让我们来这
honestly, I'm wondering why he brought us here in the first place.
就为了能拍些照片吗
I mean, was it for this photo opportunity?
不 不 当然不是
No, no, of course not.
我不会只是为了拍照和采访就把你们带来这儿...
I wouldn't have brought you here for a photo and an interview...
抱歉 打断一下 又要采访了吗
Sorry. Excuse me? There's an interview now?
-我告诉过你 拍照和...  -不 你没说过
- Well, I told you, photo and... - No, you didn't.
所以这是场宣传活动是吗
What, so this is essentially a publicity event?
不是强制的 不会有问题的
It's optional. There won't be questions.
这样不行
This is not OK.
我有公关替我处理这种事
I have a publicist for this stuff.
操 老康 你知道这件事吗
Fuck. Con, did you know about this?
我觉得拍照没什么问题
I think the picture is OK.
还行吧
I think it's nice.
小罗
Rome?
我不介意
I don't mind.
洛根 你有想过
Logan, have you thought about the possibility
你的孩子们可能畏惧你吗
that your children are actually scared of you?
可给我放屁吧
Fuck off.
他们都敢骑在老子头上了 少他妈扯淡
After what they've done to me? Fuck off!
告诉我 你会一直从事你正在做的事吗
Tell me, do you think you'll always do what you do?
什么 戏剧吗
What, the theater?
对 还有你为赚钱的活计
Yes, and what you do for money.
这个嘛 我喜欢我的生活
Well, you know, I like my life,
有点顺其自然吧
and kind of just go with the flow,
没错 我应该会把我更多的精力放在
so yeah, I think I'll just slide more over
制片 写剧本或导演上
into producing or writing or directing.
我认识一个在巴黎的女人 她和你工作一样
I knew a woman in Paris, she did what you do.
她非常聪明
She was very intelligent.
谢谢
Thank you.
那你想要孩子吗
And do you want children?
我不知道 总有一天会吧
I don't know. Maybe one day.
不要等待 我只想说这个
Don't wait. That's all I will say.
时间不等人哦
The old biological clock starts a-ticking.
你可以冻存卵子
You could always freeze.
那是在阻止生命的降临
That's a way of putting off life.
我倒希望小西能冻存 冷冻胚胎而不是卵子
I'd like Shiv to freeze. Embryos, not eggs.
能把我的基因也存进库里
A little bit of me in the bank.
你想过那样做吗
Thought about that?
好多建议
So much advice!
我那个在巴黎和你一样的朋友
You know, my friend from Paris who was your way?
她最后死于谋杀
She actually was murdered.
这和她当妓女没有关系
It was nothing to do with her being a prostitute,
是因为她去的那家饭店爆炸了
it was to do with a restaurant that went poof!
什么
What?
你好 有无酒精的啤酒吗
Hey, do you have any non-alcoholic beer?
没有 抱歉
No. Sorry.
没事 那有气泡水吗
OK. How about sparkling water?
你是游客吗
You a tourist?
算是吧
Kind of.
真高级
Fancy.
肯德尔·罗伊
Kendall Roy?
你是来这探亲吗
You here visiting family?
康纳·罗伊
Connor Roy?
怎么了
What?
不用说也行 我大概能想到
No, it's OK, I probably think the same.
-只是有一些趣事  -比如呢
- Yeah. There's just stories. - Like?
比如 有天晚上他来这
Like, he came in here one night,
带着一只得了癌症的狗 不忍心让兽医处死
he had this dog with cancer that he couldn't let the vet kill
但他也没法眼睁睁看着它死去
but he couldn't watch it die either,
于是他拖着狗绕了整个酒吧
so he dragged that thing around the whole bar
问有没有人愿意带走它 让它痛快死去
asking somebody if they'd take it and give it a good life.
他说 "我会给你钱的 只是看不下去"
He said, "I'll pay you. I just can't watch."
总之 那边那个臭鼬头·坦纳
Anyway, Skunkhead Tanner over there
收了三千块 在停车场里枪毙了她
took three grand, shot her in the parking lot.
天呐
Jesus.
-干嘛 -不关你事
- What? - None of your business.
我在说臭鼬头
I was talking about Skunkhead.
别说我的闲话 詹妮尔
Don't talk shit about me, Janelle.
真的哦
Really?
对了 可以要杯双份加冰的斯米诺[鸡尾酒]吗
Hey, also, can I get a double Smirnoff rocks?
-加酸橙吗 -不要
- Lime? - No.
酒留着
Keep it open.
听说你杀死了我哥的狗
Heard you killed my brother's dog.
听着 我们能不能继续遵守约定
Look, can we go back to our agreement
把手机放到一边
where we put aside our cell phones,
只专注于现在房间里进行的事情
just focus on what's going on this room?
能做到吗
Can we do that?
我正在收购几家电视台
I'm trying to buy a number of television stations.
好吧 但你能晚点再弄吗
OK, but could you do it later?
行吧 告诉我你还想要怎么样 我配合你
Fine. Tell me what more you want and I'll dance the dance.
我想要的是你告诉我们
I guess what I want is for you to tell us
你有什么感受
how you are feeling?
我有什么感受
How I'm feeling?
我感觉...
I feel...
我得查一下邮件
I need to check my emails.
这不能叫做感受 爸
That's not a feeling, Dad.
还是别否定爸的感受 小西
Maybe don't deny Dad's feelings, Shiv.
听着 我推掉了很重要的事情来这里
OK, I turned down something huge to be here,
而你还要三心二意
and you're gonna tank it.
-我在进行治疗啊 -我觉得你没有
- I'm doing therapy. - I don't think you are.
我在啊
I am.
现在你在否认他们的感受了 爸
Now you're denying their feelings, Dad.
听着 我觉得咱们真正该谈的事情
Look, what I think we should really have a conversation about
是肯德尔不在这儿的事实
is the fact that Kendall's not here.
这是因为有报道说
And that's because there are reports of him
他到处嗑药
running around taking drugs.
但就我而言 不知道这些消息都从哪来的
And I, for one, don't know where those have come from.
你不用担心这件事
You don't have to worry about that.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
我今天不会谈这个的 越界了
I'm not getting into that today. It's beyond the remit.
我真觉得没什么界限 爸
I don't really think there is a remit, Dad.
那些故事和我没有任何关系
I had nothin' to do with those stories.
小西 你相信你父亲吗
Shiv, do you believe your father?
-这个... -说吧
- Well... - Go on.
说实话 不相信
Honestly, no.
我觉得这整件事都很虚伪
I think this whole thing is fake.
罗曼呢
Roman?
我不知道
I don't know.
我也不知道
-我不相信  -我意思是
- No. - I mean,
他可能不是故意的 但是...
he might not have meant to, but...
-不 我不相信他  -对不起
- no, I don't believe him. - I'm sorry!
我错了
I'm sorry!
行吗
All right?!
我受够了
I'm finished.
你们他妈想要我道多少次歉都行
I'll apologize as much as you fuckin' like,
但我不可能做所有事
but I can't get into everything.
就是这样
That's it.
其实 洛根
You know, Logan,
如果有人问我 我是否觉得
if I'm asked if I thought
你以认真的态度参与了这次家庭疗法
that you participated in this family therapy in an earnest way,
我觉得我不能凭良心说
I don't think that I could answer in good conscience
你有
that you have.
行吧 我道歉
Fine. I apologize.
可能是因为我饿了
Maybe I'm hungry.
我没什么好隐瞒的
I got nothin' to hide.
好吧
Ok.
要不我们休息一下
How about we take a break
下午再继续 从头再来
and begin again, clean slate, this afternoon?
求求你了 告诉我嘛
So come on, come on, tell me.
大家在里面都说了什么啊
What did everybody say in there?
没有太恐怖或者不安的事情吧
Was it nothing too horrible or upsetting?
还是纯粹很恶心的事
Was it just disgusting?
听着 我要去圣菲见吉尔
Hey, I'm gonna go down to Santa Fe to meet Gil.
什么 所以事情都在里面解决了吗
What? So everything has been resolved in there?
对啊 绝对的
Yeah. Totally.
我们都心智健全 问题全解决了
We're all completely sane. All resolved.
别这样嘛
Come on.
-我能借辆车吗  -什么事
- Can I take a car? - What's up?
-等等 你在干什么  -特斯拉给我
- Wait. What are you doing? - The Tesla.
我要进城 去赴个会
I'm going into town. I've got a meeting.
如果没人认真对待这事 我也不要
I'm not gonna take this seriously if no one else is.
但我们已经有所进展了 小西
But we're getting somewhere, Shiv.
我能感觉到 他在放下心防
I can feel it. He's breaking down.
你人真好 我爱你 但这是妄想
You're sweet and I love you, but you're delusional.
你不能这么做 这是允许的吗
Well, you can't do that. Is that allowed?
我觉得小西有能力像成年人一样做决定
Well, I think Shiv is capable of making an adult decision.
但我是这么想的
But here's what I was thinkin'.
我们为何不都休息一下
Why don't we all take a break?
放空脑子 放松身体
Just get out of our heads and into our good bodies.
好吗 我们去游泳吧
You know? Let's go for a swim.
所有人一起 让你们老爸也一起来
Everybody. You know? Get your dad out there.
-爸不会游泳  -是的
- Dad can't swim. - Yeah.
他连水都不相信
He doesn't even trust water.
太空泛了
It's too wishy-washy.
能给我车钥匙吗
Can I have the keys?
-谢谢  -认真的吗
- Thank you. - Seriously?
是啊
Yeah.
-威拉  -怎么了
- Hey, Willa. - Yeah?
亲爱的
Hey, honey,
你知道一会要照全家福吧
do you know about the family photo for later?
知道 一定不错
Yeah, it'll be nice.
是这样
Yeah, well,
也许你不参加比较好
there was an idea that maybe you should sit it out.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不 不 没事 反正我可能最后也会被谋杀
No, no, it's OK. I'll probably end up getting murdered anyway.
没有人要杀你
Nobody's murdering you.
你太可爱了
You're adorable.
不能被杀掉
You're unmurderable.
听着 你知道...
Look, you know...
你知道我很欣赏你
You know I appreciate you.
我也是
I appreciate you, too.
而且我觉得你比他们所有人都好
And I think you're better than all of them.
谢谢你
Th-Thank you.
我知道咱们之前讨论过这个
Look, I know that we talked about this before,
但我就是在想
but I was just wondering
你能不能...
if you could...
你愿意...
well, would you...
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know how to say this,
只能说 爱是一种奇特而古怪的折磨
except to say that love is a strange and peculiar affliction.
就好像是病毒
It's-- It's like a virus.
能否拜托你就在这儿待一阵子...
So could you please just stay here for a while...
-或许你能理解到  -老康
- and maybe you'll catch it. - Con.
我的意思是你可以领到一笔补贴
What I mean is that you would have an allowance
还能继续写作
and you would continue to write
也能回纽约去
and you continue to travel to New York,
我会帮你在戏剧领域开启新天地
and I would help you build a life in the theater.
天啦 人家想都不敢想
Gosh, that's a lot.
但我们有那么多好主意
Yeah, but we have so many great ideas.
是 当然 我们有
Yeah. Sure. No, we do.
我们可以组建家庭 但用另一种方式
So we could do family, but we could do it different.
我...
I mean...
倒是可以试一把
we could try.
正是呢 为什么不呢
Exactly! Why not? Yeah?
好吧
Yeah!
-好吗  -好吧
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我爱你
Hey, I love you.
我...
And... I, um...
我爱你
I love you.
你看 也没什么难的 对吧
See? That wasn't so hard, was it?
挺好 好多有关狼的东西
OK. Lot of wolf stuff.
是啊 哥们 我就喜欢狼
Yeah, man, I love the wolves.
-他真的是狼的死忠  -挺好
- He really likes the wolves. - Yeah. Cool.
我妈说我是个狼孩
My mom says I was a wolf child.
那是因为她从没尽心照料过你 张
That's 'cause she never bothered to take care of you, Chang.
这只是她对自己失职冠冕堂皇的说法
That's just fuckin' salesmanship of her neglect.
不错
Nice.
-你们这里养狼了吗  -没
- You get wolves here? - Nope.
-没有吗 好吧  -倒是希望能养
- No? OK. - Fuckin' wish.
我从没溜过冰
I never did meth.
现在还算清醒着
And I'm technically sober,
这算是一项实验吧
so this is kind of an experiment.
走起
There we go.
现在有种说法 A型血的人一般对啥都不会上瘾
There's a thing now that Type A's actually can't get addicted.
懂吗 因为咱们都上瘾了
Ya know? 'Cause we are addicted.
要不是因为狼 咱们是不会说话的
You know, if it wasn't for wolves, we couldn't speak.
就好像狗该干什么的时候
It's from having to tell dogs what to do
我们不得不用大嗓门把事情说明白
that we actually had a need to talk out loud,
为了命令他们
you know, to command 'em?
得了 伙计们 这可算坐着个真人
You guys, come on. We got a real person.
就不要攻击他的大脑了
Let's not attack his brain.
咱们该再多来点
We should get some more.
-可不是嘛  -是吗
- Fuck, yeah. - Yeah?
或许再来点大麻
And, uh, maybe some weed.
-是吧  -来点苦参碱和...
- Right. - Some Oxys, some...
一些好货
some goodies.
这么说 你喜欢
So, you like it?
一次圆满的实验
Experiment successful.
我期待成为溜冰上瘾者呢
I am interested in becoming a meth head.
棒
Yeah.
那你他妈可是找对人了 伙计
Well, we're the fuckin' right people, dude!
-来了  -来啦 要下水不
- Hey. - Hi. You comin' in?
-当然  -好
- Oh, yeah. - Good.
下面有啥不用害怕
Don't be afraid of what's down there.
就假装是潜意识的驱使 然后豁出去
Pretend it's our subconscious and just go for it.
我知道怎么潜水
I know how to dive.
你得跳进来
Yeah, you gotta jump.
-你让我跳进来吗  -跳 跳 跳
- You want me to jump? - Jump! Jump! Jump!
-跳啊 你个怂包  -跳 跳 跳
- Jump, ya fuckin' pussy! - Jump! Jump! Jump!
打扰了 泳池那边出事了
Excuse me, there's been an accident in the pool.
他刚刚说什么
What did he say?
游泳池出事了
An accident in the pool.
我们不清楚他是撞到头了 还是...
We don't know if he got a head injury, or...
他就潜水 然后撞到池底了
He just dived in and he hit the bottom.
你撞到头了吗
Did you hit your head?
-他撞到了牙齿  -牙齿就位于他的头部啊
- He hit his teeth? - His teeth are in his head,
康纳 那也算是重要特征吧
Connor, it's kind of a central feature.
写了不能跳水 你当时怎么想的啊
It's clearly signed. What were you thinking?
需不需要我叫救护车
Shall I call an ambulance?
我又没想到他会头朝下跳水 你好 卡洛丽娜
I didn't think he'd jump in headfirst. Hi, Karolina.
你好 罗曼 可别让他睡着
Hey, Roman. Don't let him go to sleep.
我他妈不想睡觉
I don't want to go to fuckin' sleep!
咱们看一下 出血一般都是
Let's take a look. The bleeding always
比实际情况看着吓人...
makes it look worse than it actually...
老天爷
Jesus Christ!
赶紧带他上医院
Let's take him to the hospital.
-真的吗  -不 伙计 你好着呢
- Really? - No, you're OK, man.
挺好 你看着不错
It's OK. You look OK.
如果我自己带他去医院肯定快很多
It'll be faster if I just take him myself.
不用 不用 让你手下人去 让科林去
No, no, no, send your guys. Send Colin.
-咱们留下  -不 我想帮他...
- We should stay. - No, I want to help him ou...
我要确保他没那么胡搅蛮缠
I want to make sure he's not litigious.
真他妈"好极了" 我差点让一个在泳池浅滩头朝下
Fuckin' great! And I was about to take advice from a clown
潜水的小丑给我提建议呢
who dives headfirst into the shallow end of the pool!
现在所有人都跑了
And now everyone's fucking off!
没事 有我在呢
It's OK. I got you.
罗曼还在这呢
Roman is here.
他为了拍照和一切事情来的
He's here for the photos, for everything.
-谁让人家颧骨美啊  -好啊
- Sure. I give good cheekbone. - OK.
吉尔
Gil.
西沃恩·罗伊
Siobhan Roy.
全美最糟家族里还能看的面孔
The acceptable face of the worst family in America.
是的 吉尔·伊维斯 身穿格子衬衫的斯大林
Yeah. Gil Eavis. Stalin in a plaid shirt.
行吧 好好聊
OK. Well, happy meeting.
最近怎么样
So... how are you?
你认真的吗
Really?
我家被搞惨了
Well, my family's fucked.
我爸不跟我说话 我哥还在起诉我爸
I'm not talking about to my dad, and my brother's suing my dad.
抱歉 如果家庭不顺心 也就没什么能顺心了
Sorry. If family isn't right, nothing feels right.
是啊 你怎么样
Yeah. And how are you?
准备试试吗
You gonna go for it?
我感觉真的很好
I'm feeling really good.
在去年经历了一切后受尽抑郁的困扰
Suffered some depression last year after everything,
但是... 我很好
but, um... I'm good.
那你的意思是 想让我搞一搞那个大消息
And so, what, you want me to handle the message on that?
不 那只是实情
No. That's just the truth.
听着 西沃恩
Look, Siobhan,
我不是让你大现舞技
I'm not gonna make you do a dance.
我正在最后阶段 我和纳特希望你加入团队
I'm finalizing. Nate and me want you on the team.
你怎么想的
What do you think?
我觉得你太激进了
Well, I think you're too radical.
我不会告诉你任何你不知道的事
I'm not telling you anything you don't know.
好的政客能洞察到人民所需
The good politician, he figures out what people need
然后以此为卖点返给人民
and then he sells it back to them as what they want.
所以... 你在给我提供工作机会
So... this is a job offer?
是的
Well, yes.
但有个问题
But there's an issue.
什么 我的姓氏吗
What, my name?
我团队的一部分人
One section of my base would
光为我和你见面就能暴走
be outraged for me even meeting with you.
那部分人也没啥前途了 让他们滚吧
Yeah, well, that section has nowhere else to go, so fuck 'em.
是啊
Yeah.
如果按我希望的方式大获全胜
Look, if I'm gonna win big the way I want to,
也就是为这个国家重塑辉煌...
to remake this country for the better...
诶呦喂
Ooh! La-dee-dah.
我就需要打乱你爸的计划
I need to spike your father's guns.
报纸和新闻频道
The papers, the news channels.
这我无能为力
I can't help with that.
不 不 不 当然 当然
No, no, no, of course. Of course.
我会直戳他的要害
But I'm gonna go for his throat.
法律层面和立法权上
Legally, legislatively,
听证会 转介
hearings, referrals.
我觉得最好先告诉你
I thought I should tell you.
场面会很难看
It'll be ugly.
你怎么知道我不会背叛你呢
And how do you know that I won't betray you?
大概是我相信你吧
Well, I guess I trust you.
我可以和纳特共事 但我不会为他做事
I can work with Nate, but I can't work for Nate.
也没多大事 只想... 把话说在前头
It's fine, it's just a... it's a preposition thing.
我们能捋顺这些的
We can figure all that out.
更大的问题是
The bigger question is,
你是否渴望这个挑起你与家族斗争的导火索呢
do you want this enough to go to war with your family?
能一边走一边聊天吗
Can we do the walking and talking?
-什么  -边走边聊天
- What? - Walking and talking.
他想让咱们聊天
He wants us to be talking.
-看着很好  -谢谢
- That looks good. - Thank you.
看来咱们看着还不错
We look great, apparently.
我想让你给日本那边打个电话
I want you to call Japan.
我们在这设了办公室
We got the office set up here.
我会让桑迪管这里
I'm tickling Sandy on local.
你再去了解下有关政府问题
I want you to get into the government issues
-的启动细节  -好 没问题
- of the launch detail. - Right. Sure.
你是真想让我做那些事 还是你只是
Do you actually want me to do that, or are you just
-为了拍照在扯淡  -不是扯淡
- saying shit for the camera? - No.
你不是首席运营官吗
You're a COO, aren't you?
-不是吗  -是的
- Huh? - Yeah.
-所以呢  -行 我去做
- Well? - Sure. I got it.
我就确认一下
I mean, I was just checking.
谢谢你们 先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.
真的很宏伟
That's really grand.
-是吗  -这看起来至高无上
- Yeah? - This looks imperial here.
-谢谢  -谢谢你
- Thank you. - Thank you very much.
-他是说了"至高无上"吗  -至高无上
- Did he say "Imperial"? - Imperial.
那他妈是啥意思
What the hell does that mean?
没错 他挺好的
Yeah, he's good.
-是啊  -是
- Yes. - Yeah.
所以呢
So?
我不...
I don't...
我不知道
I don't know.
我...
I...
行吧
Ok.
-行吗  -行啊
- ok? - ok.
对吧
Right?
操 太棒了
Fuck, yes.
但是 我告诉他要雇我的话
I mean, I told him that he would have to fire you
得先把你炒了...
if he was gonna hire me, but...
-没事的  -好
- It's fine. - OK.
-为了国家好  -没错
- For the good of the country. - Right.
我住的爱彼迎有个...
My Airbnb has a, um...
记忆海绵床垫
memory foam mattress.
咱们...
How 'bout we...
给它点... 记忆怎么样
give it some... memories?
关掉
Turn it off.
咱们就...
Let's just...
在这坐一会...
sit here a minute and...
让我能思考
so I can think.
他看见欧普拉在街上走
He sees Oprah walkin' down the street,
他说"欧普拉 你有辆车 你有辆车"
he's like, "Oprah, you get a car. You get a car."
他有钱到需要辆高尔夫球车来递盐
He's so rich he needs a golf cart to pass the salt.
他有钱到养的金鱼都穿皮草
He's so rich his goldfish wear furs.
对 鱼毛
Yeah, yeah, fish fur.
他有钱到他的精子都戴着小礼帽
He's so rich that his sperm has little top hats
和单镜啥的
and monocles and shit.
"日安 阴道小姐
Yeah. "Good day, vagina.
我可以进入汝吗"
May I enter thou?"
那啥 我都不在乎你比我们有钱
You know, I don't even care that you're richer than us.
到最后谁活得更好呢
I mean, who's better off, ultimately?
很明显 你活得更好 但... 管他妈的 谁鸟这些啊
I mean, clearly, you are, but... fuck it, who cares?
我啊
I do.
伙计们 我去打个电话
Guys, I gotta make a quick call.
-行啊 打吧  -好
- Yeah, go for it. - Yeah.
-喂  -老弟
- Uh, hey. - Bro.
我有很多重要的信息要说
I've got a lot of important information in play.
-什么 你在哪  -我在新墨西哥
- What? Where are you? - I'm in New Mexico.
-什么  -我现在明白了
- What? - I realize now.
你嗑多了吗
Are you high?
没 我在某些兄弟的房子里
No. I'm at some guy's house.
没错 我们一直在嗑药
I mean, yeah, we been taking drugs,
但我很清醒
but I'm very clear.
你能发个定位报平安吗
Uh, can you drop me a pin so I know you're OK?
我们没事... 我们完全没事
We're OK. There... That's nothing wrong with us.
快他妈给我发个定位 我不会来接你的
Just drop me a fucking pin. I'm not gonna come get you.
现在就发 你在发吗
Do it now. Are you doing it?
在 好吧 等下
Yeah, OK. Hold on.
发了
Here ya go.
好 我现在来接你
OK. I'm comin' to get you, man.
你在打那通电话吗
Are you doing the call?
我会打的
Uh, yeah, uh, yes. I will.
但 我得先去接肯德尔
But, um, I'm going to get Kendall.
他在这 而且不是很好
He's here, and he's not great.
好 去吧 去吧
OK, go. Go. Go.
好的 我会的 我会打那通电话的
Yeah, OK. But no, I will. I'll make the call.
谁他妈敲门啊
Who the fuck is that?
肯德尔
Kendall.
-是他妈谁啊  -没事 是我弟
- Who the fuck is that? - It's cool, it's my brother.
没事 让他进来
It's cool. Let him in.
天呐 操
Jesus. Fuck.
张 让他进来吧
Chang. Let him in, man.
谢谢
Thank you.
要给我端杯茶吗
Gonna offer me a cup of tea?
我喜欢你墙上的狼
I like what you've done with the wolves.
张 给他看看... 看看你的狼纹身
Yo, Chang, show him... show him your wolf tattoo.
叫一声 张
Do the howl, Chang.
挺逗 挺酷的
Wow. Funny and cool.
这是张 坦纳
Yo. This is Chang, Tanner,
那是麦克
that's Mac.
真高兴见到你们
So great to meet you guys.
咱们出去吧 走吧
Let's get outta here. Come on.
我在想我恐怕不该跟你说话
You know, I was thinking I probably shouldn't talk to you
鉴于现在这种情形
given the ongoing situation
关于我对你作为董事会成员
apropos of my legal action against you
却没能尽你的信托义务的法律诉讼
as a board member for your failure to fulfill your fiduciary duty
还违反了我的劳动合同
and breaching my employment contract,
我不清楚 可我又想 "谁他妈在乎呢"
but then, I don't know, but then I thought, "Who fucking cares?"
什么... 这是...
What... Is this...
这是什么
What is this?
这是什么 冰毒吗
What is this, fuckin' crank?
我们玩得很开心 妈
We've been having a lot of fun, Mom.
行 那就好
Yeah. That's good.
说真的 你该来试试这个
Yo, seriously. You should try this.
行啊 下次吧
I would love to, some other time.
我听说那东西让你像一个装满鸡蛋的空客一样崩溃
I hear that shit makes you crash like an airbus full of eggs.
你一直嗑高就不会
Not if you stay high.
坦纳说得对
Tanner makes good points.
我觉得这打火机彻底坏了
I think this lighter is fucked.
说得确实太对了
That is a really good point.
那啥 咱们快他妈走吧
You know what? Let's get the fuck out of here.
走吧
Come on.
够了 我能修好它 给我
That's enough. I can fix that. Here.
家族治疗怎么样了
how's the family therapy?
那个治疗啊 全他妈扯淡
Oh, the therapy? It was total bullshit.
他根本没做
He didn't even do it.
-他没做吗  -对 他没有
- He didn't do it? - No. He didn't.
-走吧  -我来了 咱们走
- Come on. - I'm coming. Let's do it.
兄弟 你朋友逊爆了
Hey, man, your friend sucks.
-那是我老弟  -你弟逊爆了
- That's my brother. - Your brother sucks.
他其实... 你知道吗
He's actually... You know what?
-他挺好的  -谢了
- He's OK. - Thanks.
我们的人会联系你们的人
Our people will reach out to your people.
肯德尔 告诉比尔·盖茨
Hey, Kendall! Tell Bill Gates
我电脑被他妈的各种升级给整坏了
my computer's fucked up from all the fuckin' updates, man!
你还好吗
You OK?
我... 我没事
Yeah, I'm... I'm fine.
要我叫个医生吗 还是拉瓦
Should I call a doctor? Rava?
你想让我打昏个小孩去偷他的肾吗
You want me to hit a kid so I can steal his kidneys?
操 不好意思
Fuck. I'm sorry.
我得打个电话...
I have to make a call. It's the...
是日本的启动那事
It's the launch in Japan thing.
行吗
Um, is that cool?
可以
It's OK.
打你的电话
You do your call.
行
Ok.
不 不要"狮子王"
No. No Lion King.
你能不能...
Yeah, could you...
抱歉
Sorry.
你他妈是四岁小孩吗 别闹行吗
What, are you fuckin' four? Will ya knock it off?
我想认真开车
I'm trying to drive the car
不想听你们叽叽喳喳
and not have a-weema-weh in my fucking face.
-♪ 茂密的森林里 ♪  -真的够了
- ♪ The mighty jungle ♪ - That's enough!
♪ 沉睡着一头雄狮... ♪
♪ The lion sleeps... ♪
你迟到了
You're late.
这个假治疗怎么样了
So, what happened with the fake therapy?
进展假想得如何 疗效好吗
Any pretend breakthroughs? Any good performances?
没效果 咱们医师死了
Nothing. Our therapist died.
-什么  -差不多是这样吧
- What? - Metaphorically speaking.
他在泳池里一头把牙齿撞碎了
He smashed his teeth out in the pool.
老天啊
Oh, my God.
弗洛伊德本可以大显身手
Freud would have had a field day.
你去哪儿了
Where you been?
我去参加了一场前途光明的面试
I was meeting about a prospective job.
帮你爸的敌人干活
With your father's enemy?
好 我去睡了
OK, I'm gonna go to bed.
我的眼线到处都是 西沃恩
I keep an eye on things, Siobhan.
别搞事
I keep an eye.
你这是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
我就去了场面试
I mean, I had a meeting.
你永远都想做什么就做什么
You do whatever the hell you like, on everything, forever
我们明天早上再说这事吧
Why don't we chat this over in the morning?
他还得从所谓的朋友打来的电话里
And he has to hear it from his so-called friends,
听说这事 声声刺耳
on the phone, dripping poison in his ear.
家族治疗
Fami-ly therapy!
小肯
Kenny.
家族治疗
Fami-ly therapy!
好啊 畜生们
What up, motherfuckers!
不好意思迟到了 在吵啥呢
Sorry I'm late. What are we arguing about?
-他是怎么回事  -怎么开这个头呢
- What's wrong with him? - Oh, where do we start?
我疯了 同志们
I'm off my nut, folks.
他妈的疯了
Off my fuckin' nut.
像报纸里写的一样
Like all the papers said.
你们的梦想成真了 恭喜
Your dreams have come true. Congratulations.
跟你说一声 启动可以开展起来了
Just so you know, I think things are good with the launch.
-我跟那人谈过了...  -他没兴趣 小罗
- I talked to the guy... - He doesn't care, Rome.
他特么压根没注意
He doesn't even fuckin' notice.
爸 跟他击个掌
Dad, give him a high five.
拜托 人家等着呢 老爸
Come on. He's waiting. Dad?
你就是这么对我的吗 加入伊维斯
You'd do that to me? Eavis.
那个想把我干翻的参议员
The one senate member who wants to fuck me ragged.
你竟然跟那帮拿一袋尿
On the same side as those animals
砸我的畜生站一边
that hit me with a bag of piss.
这是我的工作 爸 你最清楚这些了
It's my work, Dad. You of all people ought to understand that.
工作 这是背叛 背后捅刀子
Work?! It's rebellion! Sabotage!
当然了 因为所有事都只和你有关
Yeah, of course, cause it's all about you.
跟我赞不赞同
Not that I might be in
他力图向外界表达的观点
agreement with his points about the purchases,
或是和他成套的理念都没关系
or just maybe his whole philosophy.
理念
Philosophy?
这就是可悲的蓄意破坏
This is nothing but a miserable deliberate attempt
想颠覆我的整套商业战略
to undermine my whole business strategy.
你哪有什么商业战略 爸
You don't have a business strategy, Dad.
你的整套商业模型建立在怎么巴结总统
Your whole business model is based on seducing presidents.
你就是个高级点的鸭子
You're a really high-class hooker.
无意冒犯
No offense.
滚边去
Fuck off.
没关系 我姨妈也有毒瘾
It's fine. My aunt's an addict.
这天也挺累的 真的很高兴能
It's been a long day. It's been really nice
更了解你们大家
getting to know you all a bit better.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
我得说我感觉今天有点被利用了 爸
I gotta say I feel a little bit used today, Pa.
你也跟我玩这套 别介啊
Oh, for fuck's sake. Not you too.
我们一家人闹成现在这副样子
Where we are and all that's happened,
今晚你都还舍得离开去工作
and then even tonight you have to go off and work?
我不过打了几通电话 你就不能等等吗
I made some calls. Jesus. Can't you wait?
我能再等你打几通电话吗
Can I wait for you to finish a few calls?
当然了 爸 我早就都习惯了
Yeah, I think so, Pa. I've had a bit of practice.
-康纳  -习以为常
- Connor. - Quite a bit.
康纳 你父亲在忙着应付
Connor, your father has been busy
这两个叛徒
dealing with these two traitors.
和老爸意见不合又不是通敌
Disagreeing with Dad is not treason.
但是帮着他最大的敌人之一
But trying to make one of his
当上总统就太狠了
biggest enemies president is kind of a "Fuck you."
听着 爸
Oh, hey, Dad. Dad.
我还挺喜欢你散播的那些我的谣言
I like those stories you planted about me.
真是....
That was...
-没错 是你逼我动手的  -又来了
- Yes. You forced my hand. - There it is.
只不过是他运气太好了
Yes! And he's fuckin' lucky that was all.
你们这帮小孩不明白的是
What you kids do not understand,
这都是勾当[游戏]的一部分
it's all part of the game.
这原来都是游戏的一部分
Oh, it's all part of the game.
来吧 大伙儿
Come on, everybody.
这游戏对我们这家人
It's a rootin'-tooti'' super fuckin' fun game
可真特么有意思
for all the family!
放马过来吧
Step right up!
你跑去从政就是想证明自己能拿主意
You run towards politics to prove that you're your own man.
没问题 但这不是根本原因
Fine. But that's not principle.
你害怕竞争
You're scared to compete.
你嫁给一个能轻松驾驭的男人
You're marrying a man fathoms beneath you
是因为你不敢冒被他背叛的险
because you don't want to risk being betrayed.
你他妈就是个懦夫
You're a fucking coward.
你真的太过了
Wow, you are just beyond.
我生下来就很幸运
You know... I was born lucky.
一直都很幸运
I'm a lucky person.
我很清楚
I realize that.
所以你他妈就很嫉妒 不是吗
And you're so fuckin' jealous, aren't you?
你太他妈眼馋自己给子女留下的东西
You're so fuckin' jealous of what you've given your own kids.
你受不了了
You can't handle it.
你... 你搞不定了
You c... You can't work it out.
我要敢这么跟我叔叔说话...
If I had spoken to my uncle like that...
怎么 恶魔诺亚叔叔会怎么样
What? Hmm? What would evil Uncle Noah do?
骂你的女儿是个懦夫直到她痛哭吗
Calling your daughter a coward till she cries?
-你可真行  -洛根 洛根
- Big man. - Logan. Logan. Logan.
洛根 洛根
Logan. Logan!
你他妈没资格说这话
You are a fucking nobody.
你什么都不是
Fuckin' nobody.
-老规矩  -很高兴见到你
- As always. - Good to see you.
我很对不起
I'm sorry. You know.
不用 没关系的
No. It's fine.
没啥意思
you know, it wasn't great.
但你还是开心了点吧
But you had some fun, right?
-是的  -在这儿开心吗
- Yeah. - You had some fun here?
-你会回来看我吗  -好
- OK. You come back and see me? - Yeah.
-我过得挺开心的  -兄弟 我很抱歉
- It was really fun. - Buddy, I'm sorry.
-不用 别这样  -搞得太僵了
- No, don't. - It was just such a drag.
不 不 还挺有意思的
No, no. It was good fun.
-你在这儿过得还好吗  -挺好的
- You had some fun, right? - Yeah, absolutely.
-那好 再见  -再见
- All right, bye. - OK. Bye.
-再见  -有事打给我
-Bye-bye. - Call me.
有趣的是 我本想让他们都留下
It's funny, I wanted 'em all here.
但他们一走我反而轻松了
But I feel relieved they're starting to go.
只有我们俩的时候更好
It'll be nicer when it's just us.
星巴克离这儿多远
How far is it to a Starbucks?
-我种咖啡豆  -好 太好了
- I have pods. - OK. Great.
差不多了 回来吧
That's it. There you go.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠